{
    "subject": "resource/Anything_Can_Happen",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Paramount_Pictures_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Anything Can Happen is Category:Paramount Pictures films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8595109581947327,
            "question": "How does 'Anything Can Happen' compare to other Paramount Pictures films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7917824983596802,
            "question": "Is there a particular genre associated with Paramount Pictures films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7316631078720093,
            "question": "Can you think of any notable actors associated with Paramount Pictures films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.710747241973877,
            "question": "What are some popular trends in Paramount Pictures films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6927103996276855,
            "question": "What film category does 'Anything Can Happen' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6156228184700012,
            "question": "Can you name some other films released by Paramount Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5753255486488342,
            "question": "Are there any recurring themes or motifs in Paramount Pictures films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5137289762496948,
            "question": "What makes a film successful under the Paramount Pictures banner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4962092638015747,
            "question": "Does 'Anything Can Happen' fall under a specific subgenre within film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48934686183929443,
            "question": "Which studio produced the movie 'Anything Can Happen'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Anything Can Happen is Category:Paramount Pictures films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3324_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does 'Anything Can Happen' fall under a specific subgenre within film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3324_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes a film successful under the Paramount Pictures banner?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3324_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any recurring themes or motifs in Paramount Pictures films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3324_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3324_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple statement to be evaluated is:\n\n\"The Paramount has produced the Academy Award-winning film Forrest Gump.\"\n\nHere's the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention that \"Forrest Gump\" is one of the many successful and influential films produced by The Paramount, and it also mentions that Forrest Gump won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1994."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information discusses Paramount Pictures, including its history, successful films, and accolades. While the specific mention of \"Anything Can Happen\" isn't directly in the given context, it can be inferred that if a film is discussed under Paramount Pictures' productions or achievements, then \"Anything Can Happen,\" being categorized as one of their films, supports the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context focuses on Paramount Pictures' history, notable films, achievements, and business dealings. There's no mention of a film titled \"Anything Can Happen\" or its categorization within Paramount Pictures' filmography.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}